fafsa-application.com 2015-09-07

# Professional FAFSA Filing Assistance - Privacy

A professional FAFSA preparation and filing service. Not affiliated with the US Department of Education.

At Student Aid Application Services, LLC, we place a high priority on respecting and protecting the privacy of our customers. In particular, we believe it is important for you to know how we treat information about you that we may receive from this Website, because we want you to feel comfortable and confident when using it. 

## INFORMATION COLLECTED

In general, you can visit this Website without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. Our web servers collect the domain names of visitors, and seek as many Websites do to place a "cookie" (a small data file) on your computer. This allows our servers to track statistical information about navigation to and throughout certain areas of our site, as well as to recognize your computer when it visits again. This cookie is not used to obtain your name or any personal data. However, if you prefer not to accept cookies, you can set your browser to reject them or to alert you before one is placed. 

In addition, there are portions of this Website where we may need to collect personal information from you for a specific purpose, such as to provide you with the services you request. The information collected may include your name, contact information, financial information, and/or payment information. 

This Website is not intended for persons under 13 years of age. We do not knowingly solicit or collect personal information from or about children, and we do not knowingly market our products or services to children. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features.

We may participate in interest-based advertising to inform you about our services. Interest-based advertising may include remarketing, interest categories, similar audiences, or demographic or location targeting.

We may use third party advertisements on our website to support our site. Some of the advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

**DoubleClick DART cookies**  
We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google's DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests ("interest based targeting"). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses "non personally identifiable information". It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.

## USE OF COLLECTED INFORMATION

We will send you e-mail and/or postal mail as necessary to process your order or respond to your inquiry. On occasion, we or a partner may also send you information about services which relate directly to information that you have submitted to us. 

To process your order, we need to present data to several entities. For example, for a FAFSA application filing, we would present your payment information to a payment processor to process the payment for the order, and we would present your FAFSA information to the US Department of Education to file the application as requested. We may also present your data to other entities as required by law or allowed by law. Certain statistical information is also collected from all visitors to the Website, such as the number of visits, average time spent on the site, pages viewed, etc. That data is not used to personally identify you, but instead is aggregated to measure usage of the site and choose areas for improvement accordingly. 

## OPT-OUT

We allow users to opt-out of receiving future communications and/or to have information removed from our website. Simply submit your request via e-mail to [CustomerCare@FAFSA-Application.com](mailto:CustomerCare@FAFSA-Application.com). You may also submit your request by mail to Student Aid Application Services, LLC, 4741 Central St, Ste.142, Kansas City, MO 64112. 

## LINKS TO OTHER SITES

This Website may contain links to other sites, where you may be able to access information and features offered by other parties. While we try to link only to sites that share our high standards and respect for privacy, we are not responsible for the content, security, or privacy practices employed by other sites. 

## SECURITY OF COLLECTED INFORMATION

We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with applicable law and standards to protect your personal information from unauthorized or inappropriate access. 

## CONTACTING US

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please e-mail us at [CustomerCare@FAFSA-Application.com](mailto:CustomerCare@FAFSA-Application.com). You may also call us during regular business hours at 877-207-3254. We welcome questions and suggestions about our privacy policy. 

## CHANGES TO THIS POLICY

Please check this privacy policy periodically to inform yourself of any changes. We reserve the right to modify or supplement this privacy policy without notice.
